Thanh Nguyen

© San Jose, California ம mthanh.com ⊠ nguyenhm.thanh@ gmail.com

Born 10 Jan 1992, Vietnamese citizen, United States resident, female, single.

I'm studying Computer Science and planning to transfer to a 4-year university in the University of California system in Fall 2017.

Education

De Anza - Foothill Community College, Cupertino, California, major in Computer

Science

Jun 2014-present

Foreign Trade University, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, major in International Business Aug 2010-Jun 2013

Coursework

Programming Methodologies in C++

Object-Oriented Programming and Software Design in JAVA

Advanced Data Structures and Algorithms

MIPS Assembly Language Programming

Computer Architecture and Organization

Single Variable Calculus

Multivariable Calculus

Linear Algebra

Differential Equations

Discrete Mathematics

Experience

Administrative Assistant , DT Foods, Santa Clara, California Sep 2014-Present

Freelancer: translator English to Vietnamese, data entry, web design

Dec 2010-Apr 2014

Teaching Assistant in Math, Kumon Vietnam Mar 2011-Dec 2012

Private ESL Tutor Jan 2011-Jul 2012

Skills

C++, Java, MIPS Assembly

basic HTML, CSS, markdown, LTFX

Windows, Linux, Git, Microsoft Dynamics NAV, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop

86 WPM typist, detailed-oriented, fast learner

Languages

Mother tongue: **Vietnamese**, Fluent: **English**, Intermediate: **Japanese**